# CARLOS MARTÍNEZ

# FULL STACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

linkedin: https://linkedin.com/in/coxato

github: https://github.com/coxato

website: https://<u>coxato.dev</u>

## **SKILLS**

JavaScript

React.js Next.js Node.js Express.js MongoDB Firebase Python MySQL

## **PORTFOLIO**

Git & github

https://coxato.dev

#### **ABOUT**

Full stack JavaScript programmer with more than 2 years of experience building modern web applications. I work mostly with the MERN stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node), but i have more skills like firebase, python, redux, git & github, etc. I always give my best and I am willing to learn whatever it takes.

Take a look at my work or get in touch! <a href="https://coxato.dev">https://coxato.dev</a>

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

ASX asx.mx | Feb 2020 - present

- Build modern web apps with React.js and Firebase
- Making React Native apps
- teamwork with graphic designer to implement corporate identity on websites
- build admin dashboards.

#### **FREELANCE DEVELOPER**

Self Employed | Jan 2019 - present

- build websites for freelance jobs
- make scripts for wordpress plugins

### **EDUCATION**

# **FULL STACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER**

Platzi | 2018 - 2020

Platzi is an online school for learn software development, graphic design and marketing, in this school I took the "JavaScript School" career where they teach the entire JavaScript ecosystem (frontend and backend)

you can see my platzi profile https://platzi.com/@cems/